ANTONIO JEFFERSON

Address: 4140 Highway 41A South Clarksville, TN 37043 Phone: 931-278-7688 Email: ajefferson.dev@gmail.com

Github: https://github.com/AjeffersonTN_Website: www.antoniojefferson.dev

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY:

High-energy and versatile leader successful in building, leading and motivating teams that operate in fast-paced environments. Experienced in accomplishing organizational goals, solving complex problems and developing creative leaders while maintaining a customer focused environment. Exceptional communicator with a board knowledge base of software development, budgeting, contracting, logistics, SAP and Microsoft Office Suite.

EDUCATION:

Nashville Software School	Full-Stack Software Developer Course	2018
Nashville, Tennessee		
Austin Peay State University	Masters of Science, Management	2013
Clarksville, Tennessee		
Austin Peay State University	Bachelor of Professional Studies	2010
Clarksville, Tennessee		

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE:

Software Developer

Nashville Software School, Nashville, TN

2019-Current

- Developed software development team skills through various group projects that utilized Grunt for task automation and Github for project management.
- Created and designed the Easy Communication Manager application utilizing HTML, CSS, Javascript and React.js
- Assisted in designing applications through the use of entity relationship diagrams and planning

Small Business Owner

Prime Aspects, LLC, Clarksville, TN

2018-Current

- Responsible for all aspects of company operations to include; customer relations, invoicing, accounts receivable and training
- Negotiated rates and contracts with multiple transportation clients and leased own operators
- Maintained 100% customer satisfaction rating

Health, Accident and Life Insurance Agent/ Account Manager

U.S. Health Advisors, Nashville, TN

2017-2018

- Exceeded company sales expectations and obtained all milestones for new agents
- Acquired new clients through the marketing of U.S. Health Group products and creating a referral network from existing customer relationships
- Responsible for assisting clients with their service needs to include policy changes, renewals and updates in a timely manner

Financial Manager

United States Army, Fort Stewart, Georgia

2014-2018

- Responsible for the Army financial operations through commercial vendor support, disbursement of public funds, auditing, travel allowances, accounting, financial management information systems and banking
- Managed the day to day operations of the Finance Office by providing administrative, logistical and maintenance support along with managing 33 personnel who served over 100+ customers daily
- Assisted in managing and preparing the Division budget of \$150M+ and provided weekly briefs to senior officials while serving as the Rear Division Comptroller
- Developed and mentored financial team managers that supported the Mission Installation Contracting Command; providing financial data research and contract analysis to ensure timely and accurate vendor payments

Information Technology Section Supervisor

2011-2014

United States Army, Camp Casey, Korea

- Served as an advisor to senior level executives on all signal related matters; supervises combat communications and IT Help Desk support
- Directly responsible for planning and managing the daily operations of the company communications program
- Increased operational readiness to 97% by establishing unit level communication maintenance programs, policies and procedures

Information Technology Specialist

2003-2011

United States Army, Fort Campbell, Kentucky

- Responsible for installing, maintaining, and troubleshooting combat communications equipment while providing daily IT and network support
- Managed \$1M+ in assets, materials and equipment with zero loss
- Provided weekly communications training to 40 personnel

SPECIALIZED TRAINING/CERTIFICATIONS:

Certified Defense Financial Manager (CDFM)	2016
Finance for Operations Managers (Project Management Institute)	
Project Management Institute	
Business Analytics (University of South Carolina)	2015
University of South Carolina	
Reserve Officer Training Corps	2012-2014
Austin Peay State University	
CompTia Network+ (Expired)	2011
CompTia, Inc	
CompTia Security+ (Expired)	2011
CompTia, Inc	

AFFILIATIONS:

American Society of Military Comptrollers (ASMC)